<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[blog feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[My blog to express my thoughts and views around mostly tech, but sometimes life.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 08:38:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Recommended Books]]></title><description><![CDATA[The book is designed to help you lead your digital transformation. Before we dive into why the book is important, we need to understand what digital transformation is.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/recommended-books</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/recommended-books</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloud, What is Next - People]]></title><description><![CDATA[People are the heart of every company. They are not just the customers but the employees. What is the average retention for your employees, and then look at each category of employee how does that change? How much does it cost to replace them? If you figure your migration will take 1 year, and your retention rate is around a year.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-5/cloud-what-is-next-people</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-5/cloud-what-is-next-people</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Random Knowledge - September 24, 2020]]></title><description><![CDATA[Microsoft Ignite ended today. While everyone processes and catches on a wild 48 hours. If you haven't watched anything here is a good source to get started with or if you just want "key" items, Book of News. If you want to watch or rewatch the videos]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/random-knowledge-september-24-2020</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/random-knowledge-september-24-2020</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloud, What is Next - App Evaluation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Do you know your WCAG Level? Have you even cared about it? This goes with does the ADA apply to the internet. Depending on what you read you will probably find a hard yes, maybe, and some no. It seems to be mostly on the maybe side. I know companies are being sued over it. Now with everything going on with COVID, it’s even more important.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-4/cloud-what-is-next-app-evaluation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-4/cloud-what-is-next-app-evaluation</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Azure Bicep adding the adding muscle to ARM]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you have not heard, Azure is releasing a new way to manage resources. They have created a new Infrastructure as Code Language. The language is currently in alpha, this means that you can be guaranteed that there will be some breaking changes. However, for early adopters or people looking to play around on personal projects, this shouldn't be a show stopper]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/azure-bicep-adding-the-adding-muscle-to-arm</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/azure-bicep-adding-the-adding-muscle-to-arm</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Greenwork Tools Review]]></title><description><![CDATA[This will be a general use review around 3 products: 80v Greenworks Pro 16in Trimmer (GST80320), 80v Greenworks 21in Push Lawn Mower (GLM801601), and an 80v Pole Saw. These were all purchased around May 2019 (plus or minus a couple months).]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/greenwork-tools-review</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/greenwork-tools-review</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Choose a Cloud Provider]]></title><description><![CDATA[The answer is not as straight forward as you would hope. One thing I would like to state upfront is that the cloud that people talk about is a buzzword. Its definition at its heart is someone else's computer. There are hundreds of services that make up this term &quot;cloud&quot;. If you think about it the term &quot;cloud&quot; covers everything from infrastructure services like virtual machines to web-based services like GSuite.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/choose-a-cloud-provider</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/choose-a-cloud-provider</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloud, What is Next - Lost in the Cloud]]></title><description><![CDATA[For some, the cloud almost has a mystic allure. People can think there is a magic wand and you wave it and it just works. There is no wand, and it’s easy to take some of what the cloud does for granted. One of the first things that come to mind is security. The cloud touts itself as being more secure, however, it should never be a question of if you will be hacked, or attempted, it is a question of when and how you will respond.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-3/cloud-what-is-next-lost-in-the-cloud</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-3/cloud-what-is-next-lost-in-the-cloud</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Samsung Note 20 Ultra]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is not a full review, but a general review from my general usage. I will have links to full reviews.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/samsung-note-20-ultra</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/samsung-note-20-ultra</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloud, What is Next - Process & People]]></title><description><![CDATA[Transition to Agile DevOps, From IaaS to PaaS (at least), From Monolithic Applications to microservices, The transition from CapEx (Capital Expense) to OpEx (Operational Expense), Think Global The above list is a mix of tech and business. The first one, possibly the most important is more business than tech, Agile DevOps Methodology. It is listed first for a few reasons. The main reason is that it probably is the hardest. If you weren’t following the Agile Framework for software development, you might want to look into it.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-2/cloud-what-is-next-process-and-people</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-2/cloud-what-is-next-process-and-people</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nueuralink]]></title><description><![CDATA[Apparently Elon Music has been watching too much Johnny Mnemonic. For those of you unaware its a mid 90s movie where Keanu Reeves character is a smuggler, (IMDB). He smuggles data, and has an implant that is similar to the Neuralink that is being presented by Mr. Musk. The concept is intresting and has been around for a while if you think about it.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/nueuralink</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/nueuralink</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloud, What is Next]]></title><description><![CDATA[We will be looking into the cloud and if you weren’t thinking about these concepts during your migration should be something you start talking about. The topics that will be presented all deserve their own post, and will get one, this is just to get you to start thinking about where you are and what the migration means for you.]]></description><link>https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-1/cloud-what-is-next</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.threemysticapes.com/blog/2020/9/cloudwhatsnext/part-1/cloud-what-is-next</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>